♪ HMM ♪
(SOULFUL SOFT ROCK MUSIC)
♪ PEOPLE ARE TALKING ♪
♪ TALKING ABOUT PEOPLE ♪
♪ I HEAR THEM WHISPER, A-HA ♪
♪ YOU WON'T BELIEVE IT ♪
♪ THEY THINK WE'RE LOVERS ♪
♪ KEPT UNDERCOVER ♪
♪ I JUST IGNORE IT,
BUT THEY KEEP SAYING ♪
♪ WE LAUGH JUST A LITTLE TOO
LOUD, A LITTLE TOO LOUD ♪
♪ STAND JUST A LITTLE
TOO CLOSE, TOO CLOSE ♪
♪ WE STARE JUST A
LITTLE TOO LONG ♪
♪ MAYBE THEY'RE SEEING
SOMETHING WE DON'T, DARLING ♪
♪ LET'S GIVE THEM
SOMETHING TO TALK ABOUT ♪
♪ SOMETHING TO TALK ABOUT ♪
♪ LET'S GIVE THEM
SOMETHING TO TALK ABOUT ♪
♪ SOMETHING TO TALK ABOUT ♪
♪ LET'S GIVE THEM
SOMETHING TO TALK ABOUT ♪
♪ HOW ABOUT LOVE ♪
♪ I FEEL SO FOOLISH, A-HA ♪
♪ I NEVER NOTICED ♪
♪ YOU'D ACT SO NERVOUS, A-HA ♪
♪ COULD YOU BE FALLING FOR ME ♪
♪ IT TOOK A RUMOR, OOH, OOH ♪
♪ TO MAKE ME WONDER ♪
♪ NOW I'M CONVINCED ♪
♪ I'M GOING UNDER ♪
♪ THINKING ABOUT YOU
EVERY DAY, EVERY DAY ♪
♪ DREAMING ABOUT YOU
EVERY NIGHT, EVERY NIGHT ♪
♪ I'M HOPING THAT YOU
FEEL THE SAME WAY ♪
♪ NOW THAT WE KNOW IT, UH,
LET'S REALLY SHOW IT, DARLING ♪
♪ LET'S GIVE THEM
SOMETHING TO TALK ABOUT ♪
♪ SOMETHING TO TALK ABOUT ♪
♪ A LITTLE MYSTERY
TO FIGURE OUT ♪
♪ SOMETHING TO TALK ABOUT ♪
♪ LET'S GIVE THEM
SOMETHING TO TALK ABOUT ♪
♪ HOW ABOUT LOVE, LOVE, LOVE ♪
♪♪♪
♪ LET'S GIVE THEM SOMETHING
TO TALK ABOUT, BABY ♪
♪ A LITTLE MYSTERY
TO FIGURE OUT ♪
♪ LET'S GIVE THEM
SOMETHING TO TALK ABOUT ♪
♪ HOW ABOUT LOVE, LOVE,
LOVE, LOVE, LOVE ♪
♪ OOH ♪
♪ A LITTLE LOVE, BABY ♪
♪ SOMETHING TO TALK ABOUT ♪
♪ A LITTLE MYSTERY WON'T HURT ♪
♪ LET'S GIVE THEM
SOMETHING TO TALK ABOUT ♪
♪ HOW ABOUT MY LOVE,
LOVE, LOVE, LOVE ♪
♪ WOO HOO ♪
♪ OH ♪
♪ OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ WOO HOO ♪
♪ HOW ABOUT LOVE,
LOVE, LOVE, LOVE ♪
♪ HOW ABOUT IT, BABY ♪
♪ OH, OH ♪
♪ HOW ABOUT IT,
DARLING, MY LOVE ♪